<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Seattle Tour App</string>
    <string name="pikes_place_text">Pike Place Market is a public market overlooking the Elliott Bay waterfront in Seattle, Washington, United States. The Market opened August 17, 1907, and is one of the oldest continuously operated public farmers\' markets in the United States</string>
    <string name="space_needle_text">The Space Needle is an observation tower in Seattle, Washington, a landmark of the Pacific Northwest, and an icon of Seattle.</string>
    <string name="pioneer_square_text">Art galleries, coffee shops and trendy bars fill Pioneer Square’s late-1800s Romanesque Revival buildings. Tourists explore subterranean streets on the guided Underground Tour, and learn about Seattle’s roots at the Klondike Gold Rush National Historical Park. Office workers unwind in secluded Waterfall Garden Park or grab lunch from food trucks at Occidental Square, a plaza with bistro tables and bocce courts.</string>
    <string name="gasworks_text">Gas Works Park in Seattle, Washington, is a 19.1-acre public park on the site of the former Seattle Gas Light Company gasification plant, located on the north shore of Lake Union at the south end of the Wallingford neighborhood.</string>
    <string name="hitchcock_text">Café Hitchcock is located in the historic Exchange Building in Downtown Seattle. Our entrance is on First Avenue and Marion Street.</string>
    <string name="flintcreek_text">Despite its name, the sibling to seafood-stunner Rockcreek focuses more on responsibly raised game meats (quail pate, bison hanger steak, wild boar shoulder) than on beef. Even more surprising is the quality of the vegetable dishes, like the pickled vegetables with blue cheese-tahini sauce, which make even vegetarians feel well taken care of. Together with a fantastic cocktail list and a chic 120-seat corner-space boasting a mezzanine and huge windows, this is Greenwood’s first real destination restaurant.</string>
    <string name="cafe_munir_text">This Ballard beauty’s food, with influences from owner Rajah Gargour’s Lebanese origins, is a vegetarian’s dream. Small plates of lentils ground with roasted garlic, house labneh, and sweet pears in savory tahini are consistently perfect. And the Sunday dinner is an unmissable deal, covering each tablecloth with a different chef’s-choice selection, especially delightful if the chef picks the sumac-roasted half-chicken in house pita.</string>
    <string name="un_bien_text">Un Bien has a slightly complicated legacy — using family recipes, it’s run by the sons of the original owner of Paseo, while that similar sandwich shop is now owned by someone else — but the important thing to know is this Caribbean sandwich shop is the real deal. For a good price, both of Un Bien’s bright-pink Ballard locations serve way too much for the average customer to eat, whether it’s a satisfying sandwich or a rice bowl.</string>
    <string name="baleen_text">Multi-talented couple Leah Lawrence and Billy Bartels (she formerly ran swimwear line Drifting Arrows, while he designed men’s jewelry under the label Vim Beget) opened up Baleen when they had a hard time finding affordable, fashionable jewelry that’s made in the US. Their handmade line is simple (but far from boring), and the shop is a great place to look for gifts — like jewelry, of course, but also for goods from other local makers, including Brad Curran Ceramics and Herbivore Botanicals.</string>
    <string name="digs_text">Though traveling doesn’t always lend itself to furniture shopping, this exquisite homeware destination in Ballard has plenty of collectibles that could fit in your carry-on. If you’re local — or even if you’re not, as the website lists free shipping on orders over $50 — make sure you check out the to-die-for selection of mid-century-inspired sofas.</string>
    <string name="prism_text">A great place to look for gifts, Prism is filled to the brim with things to make your life more quirky and fun, from colorful geometric prints to a ceramic planter with tan lines to a wearable sleeping bag that’s surprisingly cool. You’ll find familiar brands like Baggu and Samantha Pleet as well as plenty of labels you’ve never heard of, including specialized names like Darner Socks.</string>
    <string name="lucky_text">If vintage is your thing, you need to stop by Lucky Dry Goods. This reasonably priced and superbly curated vintage shop has two locations (the seconds in the University District) that will keep you busy for hours. Pro tip: Do not miss out on the impressive collection of vintage denim, organized by size to make shopping a cinch.</string>
    <string name="fairmont_text">In an elegant Italian Renaissance-style building dating back to 1924, this upscale, landmark hotel is a 5-minute walk from Seattle Art Museum and 1.2 miles from the Space Needle. </string>
    <string name="fourseasons_text">This luxury hotel is a 3-minute walk from the Seattle Museum of Art, 6 minutes from Pike Place Market, and 1.3 miles from the Space Needle (observation deck).</string>
    <string name="inn_text">Set in Pike Place Market, this upmarket hotel in Downtown is 5 minutes walk from the Seattle Art Museum, an 8-minute walk from the Seattle Waterfront along Puget Sound, and a mile from the Space Needle observation deck.</string>
    <string name="thompson_text">This contemporary hotel is a minutes walk from Pike Place Market and a mile from both Olympic Sculpture Park and the shores of Puget Sound.</string>
    <string name="attractions_title">Seattle Tourist Attractions</string>
    <string name="space_needle">Space Needle</string>
    <string name="pikes_place">Pikes Place</string>
    <string name="pioneer_square">Pioneer Square</string>
    <string name="gas_works">Gas Works Park</string>
    <string name="hotels_title">Seattle Top Hotels</string>
    <string name="fairmont">Fairmont Olympic</string>
    <string name="fourseasons">Four Seasons</string>
    <string name="inn">Inn At The Market</string>
    <string name="thompson">Thompson Seattle</string>
    <string name="restaurants_title">Seattle Top Restaurants</string>
    <string name="hitchcock">Hitchcock</string>
    <string name="flintcreek">Flintcreek Cattle</string>
    <string name="munir">Cafe Munir</string>
    <string name="un_bien">Un Bien</string>
    <string name="shopping_title">Seattle Shopping</string>
    <string name="baleen">Baleen</string>
    <string name="digs">Digs</string>
    <string name="lucky">Lucky Dry Goods</string>
    <string name="prism">Prism</string>
</resources>
